<resources>
    <string name="app_name">argue4me</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_argument">argumentActivity</string>
    <string name="drug_policy">DRUG POLICY</string>
    <string name="corporations">ECONOMICS</string>
    <string name="taxation">TAXATION</string>
    <string name="copy_to_clipboard">Copy to Clipboard</string>
    <string name="copied">COPIED TO CLIPBOARD</string>
    <string name="hashtag">\u0020 #argue4Liberty</string>
    <string name="coders4liberty">\u0020 \@coders4liberty</string>
    <string name="education">EDUCATION</string>
    <string name="police">POLICE</string>
    <string name="policeButton">POLICE</string>

    <!-- Please limit the arguments to 144 characters {including the author) and use twitter handles
    for attribution whenever possible, don't forget the \ before the @ and before ' -->

    <!-- Drug Policy arguments -->
    <string name="drug0">Who owns your body? You or the government?</string>
    <string name="drug1">God invented cannabis.</string>
    <string name="drug2">Drugs are not an important issue. Stop wasting money locking people in prison over it</string>
    <string name="drug3">Drugs are not an important issue. Stop using it as an excuse to eviscerate the bill of rights.</string>
    <string name="drug4">Cops shouldn\'t put their lives on the line to stop a plant.</string>
    <string name="drug5">You own your mind. You own your body.</string>
    <string name="drug6">Treat addictions as a medical issue instead of a criminal one. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug7">Nearly &#8531; of all people in prison are non violent drug offenders and more than &#189; of that is marijuana \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug8">Nonviolent drug offenders only made a choice for their own bodies \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug9">Legalization of marijuana would eliminate 1/6 of jail residency \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug10">Legalization of marijuana takes away a vital cash crop from the cartels in Mexico \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug11">Taking away a vital cash crop from the cartels in Mexico will decrease the violence in the border region. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug12">Legalization of marijuana also has the potential to create thousands of jobs in the United States. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug13">Most drug users are not criminals. They are folks who unfortunately started using an addictive substance. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug14">Look at is rehabilitation for people who want to break the cycle and become whole again. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug15">Currently, we spend approximately $33,000 per year to just lock up a nonviolent drug offender \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug16">Incarceration of drug offenders treats a temporary symptom, but does nothing to cure the disease. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug17">Drug charges on your record makes it harder to be a productive member of society. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug18">You had me at "You own your body."</string>
    <string name="drug19">Is it worth asking our LEOs to risk their lives daily to enforce these laws? \@RicMcCluskey</string>
    <string name="drug20">Military equipment has been flowing from the federal government to local police under the guise of the war on drugs. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="drug21">There will always be a black market during a prohibition. \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="drug22">End the War on Drugs! It has failed as all prohibition. \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="drug23">The civil asset forfeiture game is to steal your money. \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="drug24">How many people are really going to buy expensive Nyquil and pull the acetaminophen out of it for meth? \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="drug25">Why do we tell adults what they can put in their bodies? \@GovGaryJohnson \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="drug26">Too many unnecessary laws lead to too many in prison \@GovGaryJohnson \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="drug27"> The war on drugs has caused the violation of the Constitution and the Bill of Rights and doors get knocked down without warrants \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug28">If we legalize drugs, hostility would go away and a new relationship between police and people would form. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug29">They dont raid houses in Beverly Hills, unless youre Tommy Chong. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug30"> They dont raid affluent neighborhoods. It\'s always in the lower income areas \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug31"> All this hostility comes from the war on drugs. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug32"> The war on drugs has caused the militarization of our police forces. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug33">Because they were black, they thought, Oh there\'s gotta be some drug involved here. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug34">We need to end the war on drugs. That would put the cartels in Mexico out of business. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="drug35">If they want to look at a problem, how about looking at what killed Prince, opiates. \@GovJVentura</string>



    <!-- Taxation arguments -->
    <string name="tax0">Taxation is theft!</string>
    <string name="tax1">Good ideas do not require force.</string>
    <string name="tax2">Taxation is also the threat of armed robbery \@VoluntaryV</string>
    <string name="tax3">Taxation is also the threat of kidnapping \@VoluntaryV</string>
    <string name="tax4">Children are taught by corrupt teachers who accept that schools are funded by taxation. \@ruwart</string>
    <string name="tax5">Taxation is a threat of murder for those who defend themselves from this thuggish aggression. \@VoluntaryV</string>
    <string name="tax6">Taxation isn\'t merely theft, it\'s ongoing, it\'s slavery. \@PunkRockLiberty</string>
    <string name="tax7">Taxation is murder.</string>
    <string name="tax8">The average household pays between $6000 to $8000 in taxes and only get bigger government in return. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="tax9">Repeal the state sales tax. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="tax10">Reduce the size of our state government down to its constitutional limits. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="tax11">Give taxpayers the freedom to keep their hard-earned money and use it as they think best. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="tax12">The state can\'t do anything well except recklessly spending our tax dollars. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="tax13">Taxation is nothing but a euphemism for armed robbery. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="tax14">Property tax is renting the land that you supposedly own from the government. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="tax15">All services should be provided by the free market via either user fees or donations. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="tax16">Private businesses have a vested interest in priding services in the absence of government. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="tax17">Services should be paid for by those who directly use them. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="tax18">Business owners have a vested interest in subsidizing public services such as roads. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="tax19">The internet has flourished because it has remained relatively free of taxation \@GovGaryJohnson \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="tax20">Libertarians are probably more fiscally conservative than Republicans are used to. \@Werthertweet</string>

    <!-- Economic arguments -->
    <string name="econ0">End all corporate welfare.</string>
    <string name="econ1">Corporations control the government. Therefore, we need more government.</string>
    <string name="econ2">People are greedy. Therefore, we need a government that is made up of people.</string>
    <string name="econ3">Wouldn\'t the most libertarian thing be to let the country run itself?</string>
    <string name="econ4">Let\'s stop wasting money on pork and unnecessary programs that do more harm than good. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="econ5">Government monopoly on the water system is what made the Flint Water Crisis possible in the first place. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ6">Flint did not seek competition in the market to reduce costs while improving services. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ7">Democrats and Republicans forgo addressing the root of the problem in lieu of partisan propaganda. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ8">Free Market regulation, where mistreating customers leads to lost customers, is a natural answer to short sighted schemes. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ9">Libertarians envision a society where people may choose to share freely with one another. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ10">Free Software grants users access to the source code, and allows  them to freely change, improve, and re-distribute the code. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ11">Officials would benefit the lives of their constituents by encouraging the ethos and practices of the free software movement. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="econ12">Governments don’t create jobs, businesses do. \@GovGaryJohnson \@Werthertweet</string>

    <!--education arguments -->
    <string name="edu1">Use of "Free" operating systems and software in schools would reduce costs. \@JimFulner</string>
    <string name="edu2">Use of "Free" software in schools  provide students with the opportunity to participate in the software community. \@JimFulner</string>

    <!-- War arguments -->
    <string name="war0">Free trade with all. Entangling alliances with no one.</string>
    <string name="war1">War is the health of the state.</string>
    <string name="war2">The war on terrorism is a contradiction. War is terrorism.</string>
    <string name="war3">Are the 900 of bases the US has around the globe really necessary for national defense? \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war4">The US has been in a constant state of responding to conflicts that don\'t involve U.S. interests \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war5">Escalations continue because of the foreign policy of interventionism. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war6">Interventionism has cost the American taxpayer trillions of dollars and the lives of young men and women. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war7">Withdrawal from countries we have been stationed in for decades will save us billions in the DoD budget. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war8">Work with military leaders to determine a strategy to bring our troops home. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war9">Keep the United States out of conflicts where our citizens are not in harms way. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war10">It is time the Department of Defense act in regard to its assignment: that of defense. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war11">I will not send our young men and women into a conflict that isn\'t to defend our nation. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war12">Limit the drone program usage overseas. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war13">I cannot condone the collateral damage drones have caused many people across several nations. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war14">If we have not declared war on a nation, we should not use drones in that nation. \@CraigBowden2020</string>

    <!-- privacy arguments -->
    <string name="privacy1">Repeal the USA Patriot Act in order to preserve our civil liberties and protect our privacy. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy2">Far too often legislation is passed hurriedly, without worrying about the possible implications. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy3">The USA Patriot Act is vast, and vague in scope. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy4">The USA PATRIOT Act is all-encompassing in the power it grants the executive branch and is easily abused. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy5">The USA Patriot Act blatantly contradicting two key amendments in our Bill of Rights. (the 4th and 5th) \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy6">The USA Patriot Act creates a greater risk of the loss of freedom than terrorists pose. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy7">The only measure that can be taken to ensure our liberty is protected is a full repeal of the USA Patriot Act. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy8">We shall not live in fear of any man, most especially our own government. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy9">To ensure the rights of the American people are protected, address issues one at a time.  \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy10">For far too long, the power of the state has been used to whittle away freedom and individual liberties. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy11">The power of the state should be used to preserve, protect, and increase the individual liberty of its citizens. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy12">Protecting individual liberty is the first lens I will view every bill, proposal, program, and budget item through. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy13">Every decision I make will ask: Does this option have more potential to increase or decrease personal liberty. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy14">If a bill decreases personal liberty, expect a veto. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy15">If personal liberty is debated, expect an argument. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy16">If an existing law or policy decreases personal liberty, expect  a fight to repeal or abolish it. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy17">Make the future one of liberty and freedom for all. \@timothyfrazier</string>
    <string name="privacy18">Government exists to protect constitutional rights - not to pick and choose who should have those rights \@GovGaryJohnson \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="privacy19">There will always be anti-gov memes as long as the gov is used as a tool more and more against the liberty of the people. \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="privacy20">Is our state is going along with Federal ID to scan our drivers licenses? \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="privacy21">Now that I\'ve had the new driver’s license, I\'ve had more scans.  \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="privacy22">A lady was scanned for alcohol at about 50 years old and I was scanned for Nyquil right behind her at \@WinnDixie. \@Werthertweet</string>
    <string name="privacy23">Government exists to protect civil liberties - not to pick and choose who should have those rights \@GovGaryJohnson \@Werthertweet</string>

    <!-- gun arguments -->
    <string name="gun0">Gun control laws do the exact opposite of the very thing it is trying to accomplish, to keep people safe! \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="gun1">Gun regulations disarm innocent civilians and do not stop violent criminals from committing atrocities \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="gun2">"Gun Free zones" are nothing more than advertisements for places criminals can go to and commit their crimes. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="gun3">You should have the ability to protect yourself anywhere you go. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="gun4">Repeal all gun control laws and honor the 2nd amendment, so you can protect your family and keep them safe. \@LurieArtie</string>
    <string name="gun5"> Where\'s the NRA on this deal? This guy was a concealed carry. \@GovJVentura</string>

    <!-- police state arguments -->
    <string name="pol0">The militarization of police was made possible ENTIRELY by Congress. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol1">Our neighborhoods are not battlefields and citizens are not the enemy. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol2">The Posse Comitatus Act was created to protect citizens from the federal government\'s domestic use of military power. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol3">Congress side-stepped the Posse Comitatus Act law with the 1033 program. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol4">Military equipment has been flowing from the federal government to local police under the guise of the war on drugs. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol5">Military equipment has been flowing from the federal government to local police expanded to include counter-terrorism. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol6">Without any oversight, local police departments have become militarized using hyper-aggressive tools and tactics. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol7">Local police departments have become militarized using hyper-aggressive tools and tactics that have escalated risk \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol8">Local police departments have become militarized using hyper-aggressive tools and tactics that have lead to violent outcomes. \@haydentiff</string>
    <string name="pol9">The federal government has given them all those armaments. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="pol10">I pulled up next to this big black thing, looked like something you\'d see in Iraq, and it said MN Highway Patrol. \@GovJVentura</string>
    <string name="pol11"> I foresee a lot of this building up to a martial law situation. \@GovJVentura</string>



</resources>