<resources>
    <string name="app_name">argue4me</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_argument">argumentActivity</string>
    <string name="drug_policy">DRUG POLICY</string>
    <string name="corporations">ECONOMICS</string>
    <string name="taxation">TAXATION</string>
    <string name="copy_to_clipboard">Copy to Clipboard</string>
    <string name="copied">COPIED TO CLIPBOARD</string>

    <!-- Please limit the arguments to 144 characters {including the author) and use twitter handles
    for attribution whenever possible, don't forget the \ before the @ and before ' -->

    <!-- Drug Policy arguments -->
    <string name="drug0">Who owns your body? You or the government?</string>
    <string name="drug1">God invented cannabis.</string>
    <string name="drug2">Drugs are not an important issue. Stop wasting money locking people in prison over it</string>
    <string name="drug3">Drugs are not an important issue. Stop using it as an excuse to eviscerate the bill of rights.</string>
    <string name="drug4">Cops shouldn\'t put their lives on the line to stop a plant.</string>
    <string name="drug5">You own your mind. You own your body.</string>
    <string name="drug6">Treat addictions as a medical issue instead of a criminal one. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug7">Nearly &#8531; of all people in jails and prisons are non violent drug offenders and more than &#189; of that is marijuana \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug8">Nonviolent drug offenders only made a choice for their own bodies \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug9">Legalization of marijuana would eliminate 1/6 of jail residency \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug10">Legalization of marijuana takes away a vital cash crop from the cartels in Mexico \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug11">Taking away a vital cash crop from the cartels in Mexico will decrease the violence in the border region. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug12">Legalization of marijuana also has the potential to create thousands of jobs in the United States. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug13">Most drug users are not criminals. They are folks who unfortunately started using an addictive substance that is bad for them. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug14">Look at is rehabilitation for people who want to break the cycle and become whole again. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug15">Currently, we spend approximately $33,000 per year to just lock up a nonviolent drug offender \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug16">Incarceration of nonviolent drug offenders treats a temporary symptom, but does nothing to cure the disease. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug17">Drug charges on your record makes it harder to be a productive member of society. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="drug18">You had me at "You own your body."</string>

    <!-- Taxation arguments -->
    <string name="tax0">Taxation is theft!</string>
    <string name="tax1">Good ideas do not require force.</string>
    <string name="tax2">Taxation is also the threat of armed robbery \@VoluntaryV</string>
    <string name="tax3">Taxation is also the threat of kidnapping \@VoluntaryV</string>
    <string name="tax4">Children are taught by corrupt teachers who accept that schools are funded by taxation. \@ruwart</string>
    <string name="tax5">Taxation is a threat of murder for those who defend themselves from this thuggish aggression. \@VoluntaryV</string>
    <string name="tax6">Taxation isn\'t merely theft, it\'s ongoing, it\'s slavery. \@PunkRockLiberty</string>
    <string name="tax7">Taxation is murder.</string>
    
    <!-- Economic arguments -->
    <string name="econ0">End all corporate welfare.</string>
    <string name="econ1">Corporations control the government. Therefore, we need more government.</string>
    <string name="econ2">People are greedy. Therefore, we need a government that is made up of people.</string>
    <string name="econ3">Wouldn\'t the most libertarian thing be to let the country run itself?</string>

    <!-- War arguments -->
    <string name="war0">Free trade with all. Entangling alliances with no one.</string>
    <string name="war1">War is the health of the state.</string>
    <string name="war2">The war on terrorism is a contradiction. War is terrorism.</string>
    <string name="war3">Are the 900 of bases the US has around the globe really necessary for national defense? \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war4">The US has been in a constant state of responding to conflicts that don\'t involve U.S. interests or wars for profit\ @CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war5">Escalations continue because of the foreign policy of interventionism. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war6">Interventionism has cost the American taxpayer trillions of dollars and the lives of young men and women. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war7">Withdrawal from countries we have been stationed in for decades will save us billions in the DoD budget. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war8">Work with military leaders to determine the mission, strategy and need for bases overseas, and begin to bring our troops home. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war9">Keep the United States out of conflicts where our citizens are not in harms way. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war10">It is time the Department of Defense act in regard to its assignment: that of defense. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war11">I will not send our young men and women into a conflict that isn\'t to defend our nation. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war12">Limit the drone program usage overseas. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war13">I cannot condone the collateral damage drones have caused many people across several nations. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="war14">If we have not declared war on a nation, we should not use drones in that nation. \@CraigBowden2020</string>

    <!-- privacy arguments -->
    <string name="privacy1">Repeal the USA Patriot Act in order to preserve our civil liberties and protect the privacy of U.S. citizens. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy2">Far too often legislation is passed hurriedly, without worrying about the possible implications. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy3">The USA Patriot Act is vast, and vague in scope. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy4">The USA Patriot Act is all-encompassing in the power it grants the executive branch, that it is easily abused. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy5">The USA Patriot Act blatantly contradicting two key amendments in our Bill of Rights. (the 4th and 5th) \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy6">The USA Patriot Act creates a greater risk of the loss of freedom than terrorists pose. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy7">The only measure that can be taken to ensure our liberty is protected is a full repeal of the USA Patriot Act. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy8">We shall not live in fear of any man, most especially our own government. \@CraigBowden2020</string>
    <string name="privacy9">To ensure the rights of the American people are protected, address issues one at a time.  \@CraigBowden2020</string>

</resources>